ARTUR BAGDASARIANI

■ bagdasaryanem@gmail.com 📞 +995 597 92 91 97 in /in/artur-bagdasaryan 🖸 bagdasaryanem

SUMMARY

Strong knowledge of C# fundamentals, OOP principles, HTML, CSS and JavaScript. Seeking an entry level web developer position. Previously, two year practical experience gained in financial industry, in top audit firms. Expertise in preparing financial statements and conducting ratio analysis of real-world businesses.

SKILLS

TECHNOLOGIES: C#, ASP.NET Core, HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Python, T-SQL

LANGUAGES: Georgian, Russian, English, Armenian, Chinese

PROJECTS

Multi-layer shop

E-commerce shop application built in multi-layer architecture using repository pattern to access database. Includes features: CRUD operations, Identity framework, shopping cart, filter/search, jQuery data tables, image uploads, etc.

Mobile shop ✓

Mobile shop application built in ASP.NET Core MVC, including features like: filter/search using multiple fields, CRUD operations, pagination, modern design implemented by Bootstrap etc.

Book list ☑

Book list application built in ASP.NET Core MVC implementing CRUD operations with quite nice visuals.

React project 2

This project lets the user check popular users of GitHub in several view modes and check their repositories, organizations, etc. Written using React Hooks and Axios for making API requests.

Blog 2

Responsive website with animations, form validations etc. Made using HTML, CSS and JavaScript library jQuery.

COURSES

The Modern React Bootcamp - Udemy

Learnt React, Hooks, React Router, Context etc.

ASP.NET Core Developer - ITVDN

Learnt C#, OOP principles, T-SQL, LINQ, Entity Framework Core, ASP.NET Core

The Web Developer Bootcamp - Udemy

Learnt fundamentals of web development, advanced HTML, CSS, JavaScript

C# Development Fundamentals - Pluralsight

Learnt C# syntax, arrays, lists, interfaces, generics etc.

EMPLOYMENT

KPMG, Auditor, Tbilisi, Georgia

Aug. 2019 - Oct. 2020

Dec. 2020 - Jan. 2021

Aug. 2020 - Nov. 2020

Oct. 2020 - Nov. 2020

Aug. 2020 - Sept. 2020

• Performed audit procedures during projects within different teams. Industry background: banking, retailing, mining, real-estate etc.

Grant Thornton, Business Process Analyst, Tbilisi, Georgia

Mar. 2019 - July 2019

• Performed outsourcing of financial accounting services to firms specializing in logistics, hospitality and IT industries.

EDUCATION

International Black Sea University

2016 - 2020

Bachelor of Business and Technologies GPA 94%

SolBridge International School of Business

2017 - 2018

Exchange program in South Korea

AWARDS

Silver Medal, Ministry of Education and Science of Georgia

2016